<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>It's Null?</title>
    <atom:link href="http://itsnull.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link>
    <link>http://itsnull.com</link>
    <description>Phrase heard round the world</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2014 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
    <generator>Wintersmith - https://github.com/jnordberg/wintersmith</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>From Wordpress to Wintersmith</title>
      <link>http://itsnull.com/articles/newblog-location/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2014 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://itsnull.com/articles/newblog-location/</guid>
      <author></author>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I’ve always wanted to be able to write my blog entries in Markdown, instead of using the Wordpress editor. What can I say, I really like Markdown. I had considered writing my own small blog engine that converted Markdown to HTML. But then there goes any free time I might have had. Plus, I would have to find a hosting provider. So, there my blog was stuck on Wordpress. Or so, I thought until I read a post by Phil Haack about &lt;a href=&quot;http://haacked.com/archive/2013/12/02/dr-jekyll-and-mr-haack/&quot;&gt;converting his blog&lt;/a&gt; to run on GitHub pages.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After reading his post, I was pretty excited. The ability to write posts in Markdown. Using GitHub pages for free hosting. The whole site is statically generated, so if I needed to move to a paid hosting provider down the road, that would be easy. But then, I started reading up on both Jekyll and Octopress. They looked like they might be a pain to run on Windows &lt;em&gt;(repeat, looked like, I didn’t try it, I’m probably wrong)&lt;/em&gt;. They are written in Ruby, which I don’t have a ton of experience in. But I do a ton of JS development. So, I thought maybe there’s an equivalent to Jekyll and Octopress written in JS, using nodejs.  So, I went searching…&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Turns out there are a couple static site generators written using nodejs. &lt;em&gt;(I won’t list them, I’m sure more will be created, such is the current state of the Node community)&lt;/em&gt; I found one I liked called &lt;a href=&quot;http://wintersmith.io/&quot;&gt;Wintersmith&lt;/a&gt;. And you can see, my blog is now running on GitHub pages and was generated using Wintersmith. I’m quite happy with the results and quite enjoyed writing this post in &lt;a href=&quot;http://markdownpad.com/&quot;&gt;MarkdownPad2&lt;/a&gt;. Also, enjoyed previewing my entire blog on my local machine using &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;wintersmith preview&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I did not convert my old posts on Wordpress over to Wintersmith. Something for the next brave convert to Wintersmith, maybe. You can find my old posts at &lt;a href=&quot;http://itsnull.wordpress.com/&quot;&gt;http://itsnull.wordpress.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Old Blog still on wordpress.com</title>
      <link>http://itsnull.com/articles/oldblog-location/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2014 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://itsnull.com/articles/oldblog-location/</guid>
      <author></author>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;If you are looking for one of my older blog entries, those can still be found on &lt;a href=&quot;http://itsnull.wordpress.com/&quot;&gt;http://itsnull.wordpress.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>